To the adventurer Mr. Satou Kazuma,
冒險者佐藤和真先生
this is a heavyweight bounty target,
這是重量級懸賞目標
300 million Eris for capturing Sylvia,
魔王軍幹部席薇亞的討伐獎金
the leader of the Devil King's Army.
總共三億艾莉絲
You are already the ace in this guild.
你已經是這個公會的王牌了
I heard that you also did a great job in the royal capital.
聽說你們在王都也表現出色
In the beginning, you couldn't even beat a frog killer.
本來明明連青蛙殺手都打不倒
No!
不
Kazuma has always struck me as a man who takes things seriously when necessary.
我一直都覺得和真 是該認真就會認真的男人
The fact that his job is the worst makes it even more impressive.
最弱職業這點反而讓人覺得厲害
Hey, hey!
喂喂
You will not get anywhere
就算你們像這樣奉承我
by flattering me in this way.
也沒有任何好處喔
My best I can do is…
我頂多…
buy you the best bubble wine in this shop!
只能請你們喝這家店最棒的泡泡酒
Mr. Kazuma, marry me!
和真先生 跟我結婚吧
Sure.
好啊
Please take me in!
請你養我吧
I'd love to!
我很樂意
(Konosuba Season 3)
《為美好的世界獻上祝福！ 第三季》
ONE WEEK LATER
(一星期後)
Who made this dish?
這道菜是誰做的
Inform the chef who made this dish
轉告做這道菜的主廚
that Satou Kazuma,
葬送許多的懸賞目標
who has become famous for sending off many bounty targets, wants to meet with him!
成為熱門話題的佐藤和真叫他過來
Tell him that Miss Aqua,
請告訴他 美麗的大祭司
the beautiful high priestess, also wants to meet with him.
阿克婭小姐也請他過來
(Episode 7: Rest in Peace, The Upstart Adventurer)
(第7集 為一步登天的 冒險者獻上安息)
Excuse me.
請…
Is there something that neither of you is happy with?
請問兩位有什麼 不滿意的地方嗎
No, this dish tastes great.
不 這道菜很好吃
Therefore I would like to show my appreciation.
所以我想致上謝意
You are truly amazing for being able to satisfy my taste buds
竟然能滿足曾經住在城堡的 我的味蕾
as someone who used to live in a castle.
真是了不起
Thank you.
謝謝您的誇獎
The wine must have been added to this stew to make it taste better, right?
這道燉菜加了洋酒增添風味吧
Red wine is what makes it sour.
這個澀味是紅酒
The brand is…
品牌是…
Yeah, Romani Conti aged 30 years.
沒錯 30年的羅曼尼康帝
Am I right?
我沒說錯吧
I used discounted vinegar.
我用的是特價的醋
Is that so?
是嗎
You are truly amazing for being able to make
居然能用便宜的醋引出這樣的風味
such a tasty dish with cheap vinegar.
真是了不起
I am truly flattered.
真是受寵若驚
Thank you.
謝謝您的誇獎
The stew tastes great too.
燉菜也很好吃
But what made me applaud was this dish.
但讓我拍手叫好的是這個
This taste is like…
沒錯 這個味道就像是…
sneaking into the room of the girl I like,
躲進心儀的女生的房間
nervously opening the closet to take a look,
緊張地打開衣櫥一看
and finding the wardrobe monster inside!
發現是衣櫥怪
It is that strong
就是如此強烈
and shocking.
又讓人意想不到的衝擊
How was my explanation?
怎麼樣
Head chef, did you get it?
聽懂了嗎 主廚
I have no idea what you mean.
完全聽不懂
Is that so?
是嗎
To put it simply, it is really tasty.
簡單來說就是超美味
Adventurer Satou Kazuma gives this restaurant three stars.
冒險者佐藤和真給這家店三顆星
You get three stars from me too.
我也給三顆星
Thank you all.
謝謝你們
I will then try to get four stars
之後我會以得到四星為目標
and keep getting better at cooking.
繼續精進自己的廚藝
Saying that is brave of you.
真敢說呢
This is a thank-you gift for the tasty meal.
這是美味飯菜的謝禮
Save the change as a tip.
零錢你就當小費收下吧
I'm done.
我吃飽了
The money is just right.
錢剛剛好
Welcome back for the next visit.
歡迎兩位下次再來
I like how the head chef is easy to talk to.
那位主廚很好聊 我喜歡
Let us also ask for the most expensive
明天也在那家店
bubble wine at that restaurant tomorrow.
請他們準備最貴的泡泡酒好了
Hey, hey!
喂喂
Were we not supposed to eat tomorrow at the world-renowned eatery that serves fantastical cuisine?
我們明天不是預約了 會提供夢幻食材的名店嗎
Oh, yeah.
我忘了
I'm…home.
我回來…了
Come on, come on. You want this, don't you?
來啊來啊 妳想要這個吧
Such a perverted cross knight.
真是變態的十字騎士
No way would I give in to something like that.
我才不會屈服於這樣的東西
Please, you two, don't close the door!
拜託你們兩個別關門
It's not like that!
不是的
You have it wrong!
事情不是你們想得那樣
No, no, no, I get it!
不不不 我能理解
Aqua and I are going to eat out again,
我和阿克婭再去外面吃一次飯
or we might just stay somewhere else today!
或是我們今天乾脆住別的地方
The Axis Order accepts all kinds of love.
阿克西斯教認同各種愛的形式
Do you want me to cast a blessing spell?
要我施展祝福的魔法嗎
No, you all just do not get it!
你們根本完全沒搞懂嘛
I was assisting her with her endurance contest preparations.
我是在幫她練習忍耐大賽
Endurance contest?
忍耐大賽?
In the summertime endurance contest,
達克妮絲好像是每年夏天
Darkness always comes out on top.
都會舉辦的忍耐大賽冠軍
-Stop, stop it! -Come on.
-住手 住手啊 -來啊
If you must practice, why not at your house?
既然要練習 就在達克妮絲的老家做啦
You are making this place very hot.
搞得這麼熱是要怎麼辦啊
Recently, my father's health has declined.
我父親最近身體狀況不太好
It will make him worry
要是在家裡做這種事
about what is wrong with his single daughter
會讓他擔心還沒出嫁的女兒
if I do things like this at home.
到底怎麼了
You have not done it at home yet, right?
妳該不會已經在家裡做過了吧
It looks like my ability to handle heat has also grown
去年開始等級提升後
since I started to level up last year.
對熱的忍耐度好像也變高了
Kazuma.
和真
Sorry, help me untie this…
抱歉 幫我解開這…
Kazuma?
和真?
It seems like this scene has been seen before.
總覺得這個場面似曾相識
What do you mean?
什麼意思
T-That is…
那…那是…
Hey, hey!
喂喂
Miss Darkness, who completely embarrassed me in the royal capital,
在王都徹底惡整我的達克妮絲小姐
you are looking very silly today.
妳今天的樣子還真是有趣呢
K-Kill me!
殺…殺了我
Kazuma had a lot of fun with my fiery body.
火熱的身體被和真盡情玩弄了
Hey, mind your language.
喂 注意遣辭用句
I just tickled you, right?
妳只是被我搔癢而已吧
Geez.
真是的
Where is the powerful Darkness
在王都威風凜凜的那個達克妮絲
in the royal capital?
跑去哪了啊
What is that?
那是什麼啊
Oh dear.
哎呀
You are interested in this already, huh?
你這麼快就開始好奇這個了啊
Alright, I'll tell you.
好吧 我就告訴你
Don't be shocked.
你聽了可別嚇到
This is a dragon egg.
這是龍蛋喔
Dragon?
龍?
When I was alone at home a while ago…
前陣子我一個人待在家裡的時候
It is a pleasure to meet you.
很榮幸見到您
Who are you?
你是哪位
I have been looking for someone like you,
我一直在尋找像你們這樣
an adventurer who can confront the Devil King's Army.
能與魔王軍交手的冒險者
I was shocked
我好感動
by how beautiful you are.
沒想到您長得這麼美麗
Oh my.
哎呀
It is very uncommon to find someone as pretty as I am.
像我這麼美貌的人的確很少見
I hope you, who fight the Devil King's Army despite the dangers,
我希望不顧危險 與魔王軍戰鬥的你們
can accept this.
能收下這個
What is this?
這是什麼
This is a dragon egg.
這是龍蛋
Dragon?
龍
Yes.
是的
I do not want the wealthy to hoard it as a status symbol.
不是讓有錢人 養來當作社會地位的象徵
I want to give it to you
而是為了將來與魔王戰鬥做準備
so you can face the Devil King in battle.
我想把牠讓給你們
But a dragon egg is worth at least a hundred million.
可是龍蛋這種東西至少價值一億
No, no, no, don't say that.
不不不 別這麼說
I'd like to give it to you, the strongest of the strong.
我想讓給實力高強的你們
It's just that…
只不過…
It's just that…?
只不過?
There's nobody around.
左右都沒人
I would like to talk to you about something.
我想跟您商量一下
You didn't buy it, did you?
妳該不會買了吧
I did.
我買了
He told me that the cash I have on hand is enough.
他居然說只要我手頭上的錢就好
It is a great deal.
真是划算的交易
I even named it.
我還幫牠取了名字
Kingsford Jelteman.
金士福特·爵爾特曼
After all, I raised it.
畢竟是我養大的
There will come a time when it rules over the dragon clan.
牠總有一天會變成龍群的帝王
You all can call it Jelteman.
你們就叫牠爵爾帝吧
Are you an idiot?
妳是笨蛋嗎
Good morning.
早安
Oh dear.
真是的
I worry a lot about Jelteman.
我很擔心爵爾帝
Let's get things done and head back quickly.
快點辦完事回去吧
It is a chick, right?
牠是小雞吧
It's not a chick.
牠才不是小雞
No, no.
不不
It's a dragon.
牠是龍啦
It is a chick, right?
牠是小雞吧
I chose the good name Jelteman!
爵爾帝是我取的好名字
Please call it that!
拜託你這樣叫牠啦
Yeah, yeah.
好啦好啦
We should be doing more important things today, right?
比起這個 我們今天有重要的事要辦吧
Is anybody there? Is anybody there?
有人在嗎 有人在嗎
A major client of yours has shown up!
你們最重要的大客戶來了
Alright, hurry up!
好了 快點
Hurry and open the door, hurry and open the door!
快開門 快開門
Keep it low!
一大早就吵死人了
You must be preoccupied with your thriving business during the day.
你們白天生意興隆 應該很忙吧
We specially got up early to come here.
我們可是特地早起過來
Be sure to thank us.
好好感謝我們
Don't disturb the neighbors, you nuisance!
不要吵到鄰居啦 公害女
You came here to get that brat's money, right?
你們是來拿那個小鬼的酬勞吧
Go in and wait for me.
給我進去等著
This is the money that was agreed upon.
這是說好的錢
Be sure to thank me.
好好感謝我
I made a special effort to come here
我為了區區一個下級惡魔
for such a low-level demon.
特地騰出時間來到這裡
Quickly tell me "thank you."
快說非常謝謝妳
Shut up!
吵死了
Be careful, or I will curse you with growing aloe vera on your buttocks!
小心我詛咒妳屁股長出蘆薈
The manager has been up all night and is now sleeping inside!
現在連續熬夜的過勞店長 正在裡面睡覺
Could you kindly lower your volume a little?
能不能請妳安靜點
Is the profit really that high?
有這麼賺錢嗎
It is very profitable.
簡直可以說是笑得合不攏嘴
I have thought it over.
我想過了
What?
想什麼
The store manager will definitely mess up when she is by herself.
一個人肯定會出包的問題店長
What can be done to keep her from losing money?
要怎麼做才能讓她不出現赤字
Thank you.
謝謝您的惠顧
-I just recently learned -Here you go.
-我最近發現 -給您
that she will do pointless things
如果她太閒的話
if she is not busy.
就會做些多餘的事
-So, to keep her busy, -Here you go.
-給您 -所以我試著
I made her work 24 hours a day.
讓她24小時工作
She does not even have time to eat.
忙到連吃飯的時間都沒有
The outcome was very good.
結果非常順利
After two weeks,
持續兩個星期後
-she would start crying or laughing out of the blue, -Thank…you…
-明明沒有什麼事 -謝謝…惠顧…
-even though nothing had happened.
-她也會突然哭出來或笑出來
-Her moods became very unstable. -Thank…you…
-情緒變得很不安定 -謝謝…惠顧…
-She should not have been around other people,
-不適合出現在人前
-so I gave her a break. -Thank…you…
-所以我讓她去休息了 -謝謝…惠顧…
Come, come over here.
來吧 來我這裡吧
Although she is an undead Lich,
就算她是不會死的巫妖
you should not wear her down that much.
你也應該多體恤她一下啦
With that said,
話說回來
a curvy figure, working hard to maintain its control all day long,
日夜豐滿的身體按捺不住
every night by herself?
每天晚上一個人…
Hey, what?
喂 什麼
Do not say only part of it, it makes people interested!
不要只講一半 讓人很在意耶
Shut up!
吵死了
Kazuma, shut up!
和真你閉嘴啦
Very humiliating evil ideas!
超級羞恥的邪念
Very good.
真不錯
The girl in armor.
穿盔甲的女孩
You have a face of destruction.
妳出現了毀滅的面相
The gloomy yet dazzling, glowing girl always revolves around you.
讓人鬱悶又耀眼的發光女 一直在妳身邊打轉
It makes it hard for me to see your future.
讓我很難看見妳的未來
As a token of my appreciation for the successful business,
就當作生意興隆的回禮
allow me to predict your future.
我仔細幫妳占卜一下吧
Hey, I don't think I'm the glowing girl, am I?
喂 發光女指的該不會是我吧
If not you, glowing girl, who else could it be?
除此之外還有誰啊 發光女
Your strange mask!
你這個怪異的面具
S-Stop it already!
還…還不快住手
Don't touch my mask!
不要隨便碰我的面具
A face of destruction?
毀滅的面相?
What? You really love to act cool.
什麼嘛 真愛耍帥
Hey, that's not important!
喂 這種事不重要啦
What were you going to call Darkness at first?
你剛剛本來打算叫達克妮絲什麼
Tell me!
仔細告訴我
One of my molars is going to fall out any second.
我的臼齒搖搖欲墜
-Now I am going to ask you a few questions. -Good boy.
-那我現在要問妳幾個問題 -乖乖…
-Although it may be challenging,
-有些問題也許很難回答
-you must answer honestly to all questions. -Good boy.
但妳還是要誠實回答 -乖乖…
Okay.
好
First question.
那麼我問妳
Despite your identity as a cross knight,
妳明明是十字騎士
you have been covertly reducing the weight of your armor as of late.
最近卻偷偷減輕盔甲的重量
Why?
是為什麼
Since I am clumsy,
因為我很笨拙
I would prefer to have lighter armor
所以想讓盔甲變輕
so that I can attack enemies more easily.
盡可能容易攻擊到敵人
Darkness has been giving it some serious thought.
原來達克妮絲也有好好在思考啊
I said you must answer honestly.
我說過要誠實回答
Since…
最…
Since my abs have grown more noticeable recently,
最近我的腹肌越來越明顯
I wanted to make
所以想試著…
the armor
讓盔甲…
lighter.
變輕一點
Do you have abs?
妳有腹肌嗎
Very well.
很好很好
Next question.
那麼我問妳
That mage's dress
丟進浴室的洗衣籃裡的
that was thrown into the bathroom laundry basket,
那件魔法師的洋裝
you stole it and looked at it in the mirror,
妳偷偷拿來比比看
-This does not look good on me -telling yourself, "This does not look good on me."
-不適合 這不適合我啊
Why?
然後這麼說是為什麼
You say
而且
it does not look good on you, but when you look in the mirror,
妳明明說不適合卻對著鏡子
you smile and tilt your head.
歪著頭露出微笑
Why?
又是為什麼呢
I-It is embarrassing for me to buy cute clothes
因…因為可愛的衣服不適合我
because they do not suit me,
去買也覺得丟臉
but I saw it out of the blue
我忽然看見它
and wanted to compare it
就不自覺…
to myself in the mirror.
想拿起來比比看
I took the cute dress
像…像我這種粗魯的肌肉女
and compared it to my rough-muscled self
因為一時的邪念
in the mirror for no reason.
拿了可愛的衣服來比比看
I'm sorry.
對不起
I'm sorry…
對不…
Darkness would also look good in cute dresses, in my opinion.
我覺得達克妮絲 穿可愛的洋裝也很不錯
You do look good in a dress, after all.
畢竟妳連禮服都撐得起來
Why is it wrong for Darkness to wear cute clothes behind us?
達克妮絲偷偷穿可愛的衣服 有什麼不對
Right?
對吧
So last question.
那麼最後
There is no doubt that man looks at you with dirty eyes,
妳明明知道那個男人 用下流的眼神看妳
but you dress in ways that show off your body inside the house--
還在房子裡 穿能看出身體線條的衣服是…
Is this really related to fortune-telling?
這…這些真的和占卜有關嗎
What?
什麼
When did I say that I need to ask questions to tell fortunes?
我什麼時候說了必須問問題 才能占卜
What?
什麼
To tell fortunes, simply place your hand on the crystal ball.
占卜只要把手放在水晶球上就行了
I am just asking questions to pass the time--
問問題只是為了打發時…
I'm going to kill you!
我要殺了你
(Konosuba) Don't touch my mask!
不要隨便碰我的面具
As expected.
果然
A face of destruction has appeared.
出現了毀滅的面相
Bad things might happen
妳的家 還有妳父親
to your home and your father.
接下來可能會遭遇不幸
Your sluggish mind
腦袋不太靈光的妳
will probably lead you to act without thinking,
認為只要犧牲自己就能解決
believing that giving up oneself will solve all problems.
八成會採取不經大腦的行動
But if you do that, no one will be happy.
但是採取那個行動 任何人都不會開心
Huh?
咦
It looks like you can't do anything with your power.
憑妳的力量好像什麼也做不了
Forget about it all and run away to some faraway place.
我勸妳最好拋棄一切逃走
There, you can start over with that timid man
和想著只要強行推倒應該可行
who thinks he can get you
卻沒有勇氣跨過那條線的
by forcefully pushing you,
那邊那個膽小的男人
but he lacks the guts to actually do it.
一起去遠方從頭打拚吧
Hey, wait!
喂 等一下
Seriously, wait!
說真的 給我等一下
It seems like my friends lose faith
總覺得你每次一開口
in me every time you talk!
夥伴對我的信賴就會降低
Vanir.
巴尼爾
Thank you for your divination.
謝謝你幫我占卜
I will only partially believe you.
我就相信你一半吧
We just got a lot of money, Kazuma.
和真 我們剛拿到一筆鉅款
I think we don't need to go on any missions right now.
應該暫時不用出任務吧
I have decided to return to see my father,
雖然我並不在意占卜的內容
despite the fact that I am unconcerned about the fortune-telling.
但我決定回去見見久違的父親
Okay.
好
Kid.
小鬼
I have some new advice for you.
我給你新的建言
Do not be happy just because you got a reward,
你別因為收到酬勞就覺得滿足
you should make more products that sell well instead.
應該製作更多熱賣的商品
I told that girl,
我對那個女孩這麼說了
"It looks like you can't do anything with your power."
憑妳的力量什麼也做不了
However, based on your efforts,
但是根據你的努力
it is possible that you are capable of doing something.
也許並非什麼也做不了喔
Take this!
看我的
What's this?
什麼跟什麼啊
Even in the summer, you will not be shedding any fur, will you?
你到了夏天也不會掉毛呢
Kazuma!
和真
What the heck! You startled me!
搞什麼 嚇我一跳
It is time to go after those bounty monsters!
我們去狩獵懸賞怪物吧
Being a young woman who is not married,
妳好歹也是還沒出嫁的大小姐
you should not be going out all the time at night.
夜遊也該有個限度
I am not going out for no reason, you idiot!
笨蛋 我才不是去夜遊
Look at this!
比起那種事
Multihead Water Snake?
多頭水蛇?
It's a heavyweight bounty monster.
是重量級懸賞怪物
Some days ago,
就在前幾天
the water snake that was sleeping at the lake's bottom seemed to wake up.
沉睡在湖底的水蛇好像醒來了
That is what you wanted to hunt?
居然要狩獵這種東西
It is too early in the morning
妳不要因為現在是一大早
to start talking big.
就說夢話啦
Do you not want to protect Axel?
難道你不想守護阿克塞爾嗎
Come on, Satou Kazuma, the hero who defeated many
打倒許多魔王軍幹部的勇者
of Leaders of Devil King's Army.
佐藤和真
It is your time to shine.
來吧 現在是你出場的時刻
You think I will agree with you
妳以為只要說我是勇者之類的
if you call me a hero?
我就會同意嗎
I have made enough cash already.
我已經賺夠錢了
Nothing else?
沒有嗎
Isn't there anything that can make me more motivated?
沒有能讓我更充滿幹勁的事嗎
What?
什…
You should know me well since we have
我們認識這麼久了
known each other for a long time.
妳應該知道吧
I-I get it.
我…我知道了
If we successfully hunted it,
討伐成功之後
as a reward…
作為獎勵…
Um…
那個…
What?
什麼
What do you want to give me?
妳到底打算做什麼
I will kiss your cheek.
我就親你的臉頰
Rejected.
駁回
What?
什麼
These days, no one would risk their life just for a kiss.
現在哪有人會為了區區一個吻 就賭上性命啊
J-Just for a kiss?
區…區區一個吻?
Hey, Chomusuke.
喂 豆之助
This woman
這位大姊姊
seems to really think that her one kiss
好像認真以為自己的一個吻
could make a man risk his life.
就能讓男人賭上性命喔
How much self-esteem does she have?
她到底有多自視甚高啊
Y-You jerk!
你…你這傢伙
How dare you take advantage of me?
竟敢得了便宜還賣乖
Hey, stop it!
喂 住手
I am against violence!
我反對暴力
Hey.
我說
Can't we go?
無論如何都不行嗎
(Konosuba) She is actually begging me…
居然哀求我…
Isn't she getting smart?
這不是變高明了嗎
I don't want to!
不要
I am not interested in looking for water snakes!
我才不要去找什麼水蛇
Darkness, why do you want to subdue a bounty target?
為什麼達克妮絲要去討伐懸賞目標
Are you really a penniless noble?
妳該不會真的是貧窮貴族吧
-When you talk about water snakes, you automatically think of dragons. -I don't want to, I don't want to!
-說到水蛇就會想到龍 -我不要 我不要
-Just beating it -Why do I have to do it?
-只要打倒牠就能光明正大 -為什麼要去啊
would let me call myself a dragon slayer!
自稱是屠龍者了
I want to be known as the "dragon slayer"!
我要得到屠龍者這個別稱
We will be able to raise dragons at home after Jelteman is born!
爵爾帝出生後 我們就能在家裡養龍了
Why do you want such a terrible title?
妳為什麼想要那種可怕的稱號啊
Also, why do I have to leave Jelteman with Wiz's shop?
再說我為什麼非得把爵爾帝 寄放在維茲的店裡不可啊
-What can we do? -Why?
-有什麼辦法 -為什麼…
-We cannot ask anyone else for hatching eggs,
-孵蛋這種蠢事
-that would be silly. -Why?
-又沒有其他能拜託的人 -為什麼…
It worries me that entrusting it to Lich and the demon
竟然把牠交給巫妖和惡魔保管
will have a bad effect on Jelteman!
我擔心會給爵爾帝帶來壞影響
Listen up.
聽好了
The longer a mother dragon carefully holds an egg,
龍蛋這種東西
the more powerful the magic it will receive,
被母龍小心翼翼抱在懷裡越久
and it will take on the traits
就能得到越高的魔力
of both its parents!
並繼承父母的屬性
I really hope it hatches into a sacred white dragon.
我明明希望牠孵化成神聖的白龍
-It could be affected by the darkness -Thank…you…
-牠說不定會受到黑暗影響 -謝謝…惠顧…
and hatch into a black dragon or something!
孵化成黑龍之類的
Then let us quickly beat the water snake and go back.
那我們就快點打倒水蛇回去吧
Alright then.
真拿你沒辦法
Then I'll go have a look.
那我去看看吧
Let us run away right away
如果惠惠的魔法行不通
if Megumin's magic does not work.
我們就立刻逃回去吧
(Konosuba) Okay, let us start.
OK 作戰開始
She is not playing in the water, right?
她是在淨化吧
She's purifying it, right?
並不是在玩水
Because monsters hate clean water.
因為怪物討厭乾淨的水
Please cast your Explosion magic
阿克婭把水淨化 引出水蛇後
after Aqua has purified the water and lured the water snake.
就麻煩妳施展爆裂魔法
Hey.
喂
That Aqua
阿克婭那傢伙
has started to sleep right above where the heavyweight
在重量級懸賞目標沉睡的地方上面
bounty target was.
開始睡午覺了
Are we going to tie her up with a rope first
為了防止她漂走
to keep her from floating away?
是不是應該事先綁上繩子呢
Here it comes!
來了
I feel a huge amount of magic power!
我感覺到龐大的魔力
Aqua!
阿克婭
Time to wake up!
妳要睡到什麼時候
Wake up quickly!
快醒醒
-Aqua, look below! -Aqua, wake up!
-阿克婭 看下面 -阿克婭 快醒醒
-So noisy. -Hurry up and get out of the water.
-吵死了 -快點離開水裡
Look.
看啊
Water has been thoroughly purified.
水已經被淨化得很乾淨了
Then I should also leave the lake.
那我也差不多該離開湖裡了
Mr. Kazuma!
和真先生
It seems like something huge is approaching!
好像有什麼很巨大的東西正在接近
No, please!
不要啊
I want to go home!
我想回家
I want to go home already!
我已經想回家了
Aqua!
阿克婭
No way!
不行
It is not possible for me to use explosive magic right now!
這樣子我不能施展爆裂魔法
Mr. Kazuma!
和真先生
I really want to go home!
我好想回家啊
-This guy… -I want to go home…
-這傢伙 -我想回家…
-This is not good…
-很不妙啊
(Episode 8: Eternal Rest to The Lord of This Lake)
(第8集 為這個湖的 主人獻上永眠)
I am Beldia.
我是貝爾迪亞
Is that guy named Satou Kazuma?
是叫佐藤和真嗎
I sometimes hear about what he did.
我偶爾會聽到他的事蹟
He's still alive…
他居然還活著…